www.aaronrobson.uk

https://github.com/aaronrobson

## Personal Statement

I consider myself to be an organised software developer. I do my utmost to keep up with developments in the field, new techniques, libraries and languages; in order to make more informed decisions. To keep on top of open issues I log them with detailed reproduction steps, so that myself and my colleagues can hit the ground running in resolving them.

My programming experience is primarily in Python, Delphi, C#, SQL, and Haskell though I have experimented with Scheme Lisp and Prolog. I have worked on several personal projects including an implementation of John Conway's Game of Life and a numeric base converter.

As much as I enjoy programming I am a social person who enjoys catching up with my colleagues over a meal out. Outside of work I like going on cruises and cycling holidays.

## **Employment**

Wheatley Solutions Ltd.

2016-Present

Delphi Software Developer

Bacton, Suffolk

Working with Delphi, C# and Oracle PL/SQL database projects.

Digi Europe Ltd.

2010-2016

Software Engineer

Haverhill, Suffolk

Developing and maintaining current software whilst building bespoke solutions. Control of and information collection from weighing and labelling machines. Vast experience of meeting customers to discuss future development projects and visiting customer's sites for software maintenance.

I have developed some in-house utilities in Python and Haskell to improve my own work-flow and to help the development team, these include a log file analyser.

## Education

University of Lincoln

2007-2010

Software Engineering B.Sc.

Lincolnshire

During my time at University I had the opportunity within a team to build a web based holiday booking system. I also built a blog based on the principles of CRUD.

In the Mobile and Distributed Computing unit I learnt a lot by the challenge of developing a C# chat program.

Hills Road Sixth Form College

2005-2007

College

Cambridge

A-Levels in Computing, Maths and Chemistry (grades B, C and D respectfully).

AS-Levels in Physics and Critical Thinking.

Witchford Village College

2002-2005

Secondary School

Ely, Cambs

Nine GCSEs grade C and above, including an A\* in Maths and an A in both Science and English.

Technical Reading Books I have enjoyed reading:

Brain of the Firm, The Mythical Man-Month, The Pragmatic Programmer, Surely

You're Joking Mr Feynman, Peopleware, Slack, The Design of Everyday Things, Paul Graham and Dijkstra's essays.

**References** Available upon request.